<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
<title>Bad Luck to the Rolling Water</title>
<artist>Lankum</artist>
<structure>C-V1-C-V2-C-V3-C-V4-C-V5-C-V6-C</structure>
<chorus><![CDATA[Bad luck to the rolling water, bad luck to the salty brine,
I only had the one true love, she swore she would be mine.
Now she’s gone and left me and wandered far away,
Left me crying here beside the water.]]></chorus>
<verse><![CDATA[
Well Nancy Doyle it was her name, she was a fine young lady,
Until she sailed away from me and she almost drove me crazy.
Well Nancy came from Dublin town, right beside the Poddle,
‘Til o’er the sea away from me she chanced all for to toddle.]]></verse>
<verse><![CDATA[Her eyes were wild and shone bright blue, her laugh was full and hearty,
Her humour droll, the life and soul and centre of every party.
She could drink a pint of whiskey all straight from the can,
When the night was done and dusted it was then she’d hold my hand.]]></verse>
<verse><![CDATA[She might not have been Aurora, a Flora or Diana,
But she sang songs in the back tap room along to the ould piana.
She was not Euternatia, nor was she Venus bright,
But she could drink much more than you and beat you in a fight.]]></verse>
<verse><![CDATA[Well there she was at work one day pretending to be sober,
When up there steps a dandy gent all for to look her over.
He says ‘I have an offer - I think you’ll find it grand!
We’ll sail away upon the sea smuggling contraband.’]]></verse>
<verse><![CDATA[What could I say, what could I do? It was more than I could offer,
I had to let her spread her wings, I couldn’t try to stop her,
Now she collects fine diamonds vases and antique rugs,
With the all the bags of money that she makes from dealing drugs.]]></verse>
<verse><![CDATA[Oh Nancy, dearest Nancy, one thousand times adieu,
I’ll ne’er forget ‘til my dying breath the times I spent with you.
Though now I’m old and feeble and shaking on each knee,
If ever you come this way again we’ll go upon a spree.]]></verse>
</song>
