<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
<title>Barrett's Privateers</title>
<artist>Stan Rogers</artist>
<structure>V1-C-V2-C-V3-C-V4-C-V5-C-V6-C-V7-C-V8-C-V9-C</structure>
<chorus><![CDATA[God damn them all!
I was told we'd cruise the seas for American gold
We'd fire no guns, shed no tears
I'm a broken man on a Halifax Peer
The last of Barrett's Privateers]]></chorus>
<verse><![CDATA[Oh, the year was 1778
( "How I wish I was in Sherbrook now!")
A letter of mark came from the King
To the scummiest vessel I'd ever seen]]></verse>
<verse><![CDATA[Well, Elcid Barrett cried the town
( "How I wish I was in Sherbrook now!")
For twenty brave men all fisherman who
Would make for him the "Antelope's" crew]]></verse>
<verse><![CDATA[The "Antelopes" sloop was a sickening sight
( "How I wish I was in Sherbrook now!")
She had a list to the port and her sails in rags
And the cook in the scuppers with the staggers and jags]]></verse>
<verse><![CDATA[On the king's birthday we put to sea
("How I wish I was in Sherbrook now!")
It was ninety one days to Montigo Bay
Pumping like madmen all the way]]></verse>
<verse><![CDATA[On the ninety sixth day we sailed again
( "How I wish I was in Sherbrook now!")
When a bloody great Yankee hove in sight
With our cracked four-pounders we made to fight]]></verse>
<verse><![CDATA[The Yankee lay low down with gold
( "How I wish I was in Sherbrook now!")
She was broad and fat and loose in stays
But to catch her took the Antelope two whole days]]></verse>
<verse><![CDATA[Then at length we stood two cables away
( "How I wish I was in Sherbrook now!")
Our cracked four-pounders made an awful din
But with one fat ball the Yank stove us in]]></verse>
<verse><![CDATA[The Antelope shook and pitched on her side
( "How I wish I was in Sherbrook now!")
Well Barrett was smashed like a bowl of eggs
And the Maintruck carried off both me legs]]></verse>
<verse><![CDATA[So here I sit in my twenty-third year
( "How I wish I was in Sherbrook now!")
It's been six years since I sailed away
And I just made Halifax yesterday]]></verse>
</song>
